how to sit so I take out more of the
screen my shirt also says hope or I hope
actually says helping screw this up name
of Kyle sees his book but number 15 that
I was trying to talk about last video
but I got my brain got hijacked but my
heart let's say that flipping the whole
dialogue around trash which aren't meant
to talk about was the fact that how we
create things now is we have a someone
who has an idea they create a product
they have to create their certain amount
of them to put them in stores then
people decide like they find out through
the market whether people like it
whether its branded right whether it
looks all of that there are so many in
efficiencies in that cycle that we can
definitely address one of the big ones
is the exchanging that so instead of
saying I'm a producer I'm going to
produce X number of cogs you say I am a
called user I use this many copies a
year please make them for me where can I
get them made that they fit what I want
to have and so you reverse it so it does
it you can't get things as instantly but
you're able to have a feedback cycle so
maybe you do eventually realize that
there's a million cogs that need to be
made per day per year and have them
ready to go and when it exceeds that
sorry you're waiting because they're in
the next product cycle but you're not
making ten million hoping that million
sell every month and I believe that's a
much better way of doing it there's less
it just works better on every level and
the more you're able to communicate what
it is you actually want your gob how
many cog things I look things are going
to go
economics use a lot of cob knowledge
ease cog examples so flipping it being
able to say okay well I mean Kickstarter
kinda does that when kids Turner comes
up with something in there is going to
sell ten thousand items but then it ends
up getting more because they're not just
saying I'm going to sell ten thousand
who am i selling into are running ten
thousand it is kind of the opposite
where they're saying how many people
would want this if we made it if ten
thousand say yes then we do ten thousand
100,000 100,000 and but doing that it's
doing that for projects where it's like
okay and it can be anything from like I
will make some help the pants that look
like this that are like this this size
are you this size and it will like send
a get everything all together in jumbled
but send outer is why we need a hold of
them interconnected send out a email or
alert to everyone who is that sighs hey
do you want to do want these yoga
instead of being like oh I like those
gobo pants
do they have them in my size you have
someone who has actually creating them
for that size specifically is because
we're creating a thousand of them at
that exact size it's super cheap Scott
could quality whatever happens to be
that you value then it's offering you or
it is someone who's making you know 100
in every size do you want one of those
hundred and then anyway so figuring out
as a user how many are needed and wanted
and then creating that many and doing
that in the most efficient manner and
being able to help all the way long
lines if you're a producer of it if you
want to make a small batch of things and
sell them who would most be able to use
them what's the price point all of if
you make ten thousand for people is that
feasible but also like cannot bring the
price point down and so I think that
flipping the trash system instead by
saying we're not going to create things
that aren't usable because people don't
want them rocking over produce say it's
stopping the overproduction of items as
I did worth it